"London"
"DEM Industries Headquarters"
What the hell were you
thinking, Mr. Westcott?
I don't understand what
you're asking, Murdoch.
I wish you'd stop playing dumb.
I'm asking about all the
things you did in Japan.
Interfering with the Self-Defense Force...
Using Wizards and equipment
for your own agenda, and worse...
Making the city a warzone!
The Japanese government is all over us.
How will you rectify this situation?!
It's no matter.
We achieved enough to make it worthwhile.
We succeeded in Princess's inversion.
Do you not understand what I'm saying?
What do Spirits have to do with saving DEM?
The company can't afford to take
a backseat to your selfish desires!
Everyone, the time has come!
I petition that Managing Director
Westcott be dismissed!
And you're fine with this, sir?
Of course.
After all, doing so is a right
of the board of directors.
Come, Chairman Russell!
Let us take a vote this instant!
Very well. A raise of hands to dismiss him.
Zero hands.
His dismissal is rejected.
Wh-What are you talking about, Chairman?!
All these people agree with--
You'll find Realizers ready in the infirmary.
If you get there quickly, you'll be
back to normal in a few days.
And once I fulfill those selfish
desires you spoke of,
I'll hand over the company.
It won't be long now.
Not when compared to how
long we've been waiting.
A written challenge...
And with it, 12 pictures.
She asks this...
Can you find me?
So, these must be the
pictures that Natsumi sent.
"Episode Two:
'Can You Find Me?'"
"Among them, I'm there.
Can you guess who I am?
Before everyone is gone."
That was Natsumi's message.
If we take it at face value...
Natsumi is impersonating one of these 12,
and if you can't find her,
they will disappear one
after another, or so it seems.
Most likely.
Though, she makes no mention of
a time limit or methods you can't take.
I can't imagine she simply
forgot to write that.
While you're puzzled and overwhelmed,
she's probably overseeing
the game from somewhere.
No... It may not be safe to call this a game.
Those erased by Natsumi...
...we can't guarantee will come back safe.
That's true. Taking Kurumi, for example...
Natsumi may not be so friendly
as to horse around and play games.
Someone here may already
be gone for eternity...
No...
Natsumi isn't like that.
If I can just guess who she's impersonating,
they'll come home in one piece.
You're sure giving Natsumi your full trust.
If it were you,
would you open up your heart
to someone who doesn't trust you?
Look at you, talking so big...
Though, it's exactly like you say.
Mmm...
Either way, we should hurry.
I'm sorry, Kotori, but stay
away from command.
It's only natural.
There's still the possibility
that I'm Natsumi.
And you, Shin...
You have lots of work ahead of you.
What should I do?
For the time being,
start by deciding which
order you'll date them in.
To see through Natsumi's disguise,
you must not overlook even the
smallest difference from the norm.
You'll date them one by one
to check if anything seems off.
I feel like it's wrong to go
on dates while doubting people...
Good morning, Shido!
Sorry! Did you wait long?
Nope. You're right on time.
It's Tohka no matter how you look at it.
What's wrong, Shido?
You don't seem very lively today.
Eh? Y-You think?
I'm normal, normal!
Try to relax, Shin.
Even supposing she's Natsumi,
she wouldn't give it away so easily.
Let's try to shake her up a bit.
Hey, Tohka.
Remember the last time
we went out? When was it?
Huh? What are you talking about?
Weren't we shopping together
just a few days ago?
Ah, oh, yeah...
She got it. Next is...
But I don't mind going out
no matter how much.
Because it's fun and makes me happy!
Tohka...
Hmph... What a performance.
Huh?
You're just like Tohka.
Right, Natsumi?
You...
Don't tell me...
Shido! Who's this Natsumi?
Eh?
I'm asking you who this woman
you named just now is!
Where's this woman of yours, Shido?!
No, that was...
A-A greeting! A greeting!
From an island down south!
It caught on in Japan, too!
Natsumi! Natsumi! You know?
Is that right?
What an incredible lie...
It's so bad, it could be real...
I see! So it's just a greeting!
So when people say "Natsumi,"
what does it mean?
Um...
"Th-That I love you," I think...
Oh, I see!
And? What did you mean by
"You're just like Tohka"?
Eh?!
Hmm?
--Wow! Look, Tohka! That restaurant
is doing a lunch buffet!
--Huh?
--Wow! Look, Tohka! That restaurant
is doing a lunch buffet!
It'd be a waste if we didn't eat there!
Lunch, huh? I don't mind, but...
All right! Let's go then!
It's lunch, and yet... What's this reaction?
Normally, that'd be enough
to cheer her up instantly...
As of yet, no detection of Natsumi.
Have you felt anything?
I'm thinking it's gotta be Tohka...
But we're here for lunch, and she seems so...
What's wrong?
Something the matter, Shido?
Uh, no...
No way! Tohka only got that much?!
Do you think she's sick or something?
Absurd! That hungry monster
is a bottomless pit!
Hey... Aren't you eating?
Let's eat up.
R-Right... Let's eat.
You don't think... Tohka is really Natsumi?
Thanks for the meal.
Eh? Already?
What's wrong, Tohka?
That can't possibly be enough for you.
I-It's okay.
I saw on TV yesterday...
Be careful!
Girls who eat lots more than guys...
...can sometimes be a turn off!
I didn't want Shido to be turned off by me...
So, I...
Actually, I prefer girls who
can happily eat lots of food.
Huh? Really?!
I knew it had to be Tohka after all.
Yeah... But we can't dismiss her yet.
Stay with Tohka a bit longer,
but get back home by at least 3 o'clock.
Your next date will come to visit you.
"Out of food for today"
Yeah, I'm coming!
Boo!
Be a little more careful, Shido!
Th-Thanks.
Wait... Yoshinon, right?
Hi! It's everyone's idol, Yoshinon!
Sorry, Yoshino.
Yoshinon surprised me, so...
T-Trick or treat.
If you don't give candy,
I have to prank you...
Shido, this is...
Never thought you'd come
here trick or treating.
We're kinda out of candy.
Hope you're not offended by hotcakes.
This is a first for me... hotcakes.
I see... Well, help yourself.
You had the same reaction
the first time you came here.
Um...
What was it you ate back then?
That was...
You made oyakodon for me.
Ah, yeah, right.
Eh? What's this about, Shido?
That doesn't ring a bell to me.
You don't remember?
No...
Could it be... Was that when
I stayed over at Origami's?
Oh, yeah, that happened...
I had to invade Origami's
place to get you back.
Huh? But...
C'mon, just do it.
Shido...
We can split it.
Eh? No, it's okay.
I made those for you, so...
A-All right, all right.
I'll eat it.
Ah!
A-Ah...
Was it yummy?
Yup! Very yummy!
Uh...
Shido, there's syrup...
Hmm? On me?
Ooh!
Hotcakes are like, halfway
between food and candy, so...
That's why I...
It was a prank!
Whew, whew! You go girl, Yoshino!
Reine...
You think... that was
the real Yoshino, right?
Well, who knows?
So? Who's my next date?
Right. Hiroto Tonomachi.
Tohka, Yoshino, and third,
Hiroto Tonomachi...
None of their behavior or memories
seemed much different than usual.
That whole thing with Tonomachi
I'd prefer to not call a date...
Shin, just one more for the day.
Yuzuru is already waiting at the spot.
Understood.
Sorry, Yuzuru!
Offended.
You have some nerve calling
me here and arriving late.
Sorry! Was running a bit late!
Pardon. It's all right.
I have a big heart, so...
We'll call those five minutes a fluke.
Does it not seem enough with only me here?
Eh? N-No, that's not it.
I was just thinking how rare it is...
Negative. Don't feel as if
you need to make an excuse.
Kaguya and I are of one heart and mind.
In fact, your statement...
It validates how closely she
and I are bound together.
Question.
By the way, what's the matter?
Calling me out this late...
Oh, nothing...
Thought it'd be nice to talk
with you alone once in a while...
Bad idea?
Negative. It's not a bad idea at all.
But if it's like that...
Y-Yuzuru?
Selfish. Just for tonight, Shido is all mine.
Isn't that right?
Suggestion.
Shido, shall we take a walk?
Whoa...
Admiration. It's so beautiful.
Yeah, it sure is.
Point. If a girl says something is beautiful,
it's common knowledge the guy
should say "But you're more beautiful."
Is that how it is?
Agreement. That's how it is.
But you're more beautiful.
Smile. Is that true?
Uh...
Address.
Shido...
Wh-What?
Question.
Shido... Between Kaguya and me,
who do you like more?
I can't pick when you ask so suddenly...
You're both precious.
Scorn. Good grief.
You picked the most pathetic
and weak answer there was.
Sh-Shut up. When you
ask that, all of a sudden...
Confirmation.
Then, if I gave you enough time,
would you be able to answer?
In that case, what answer
did you wanna hear?
Answer.
Had you picked Kaguya,
I would've called you a good boy.
But if you had picked me... Hmph!
I learned something new...
Addition.
But, if you had picked me...
...I'd be happy.
Then, which is it in the end?
Sigh. It's just like I said.
I wouldn't mind you choosing either of us.
However, you answered like a chicken.
You disappoint me, Shido, you big buffoon.
Ugh...
Though...
Petition.
If... Just if...
If Kaguya ever asks you
the same question I did...
When the time comes,
tell her that you choose Kaguya.
Prediction. Kaguya will get mad at you.
She'll ask why you didn't pick me.
But, deep inside she'll be so happy it hurts.
Yuzuru...
Confidence.
Kaguya behaves like she does,
but she loves you very much.
It's me saying it, so it must be true.
The things that Kaguya hates, I also hate.
Likewise, the things that I love...
...Kaguya also loves, too.
Careless. I said more than I should have.
Before I say anything more, I should go.
Y-Yuzuru...
Petition. What I said is no lie.
Kaguya is extremely taken with you, so...
Please take care of Kaguya for me!
H-Hey, Yuzuru! Yuzuru!
And? You came home after that?
After a date, making a girl walk
home at night all by herself...
...is not exactly a choice
I'm impressed with.
Sorry. It happened so fast...
There's not much you could've done.
From start to finish,
Shin worked hard today.
I know that full well.
Going on four dates in a single day
isn't such an easy schedule.
So? Your thoughts?
Tohka, Yoshino, Tonomachi, Yuzuru...
From your perspective,
was Natsumi impersonating anyone?
Mmm...
I can't say for sure.
I want to believe everyone was real, but...
Well, it's wishful thinking
that it would be easy.
There's no suspicious readings
from Fraxinus' analysis either.
Until we get more data from
the next round of dates,
it's anyone's guess.
Anyways, go and get some rest.
Don't want you to be sleep deprived.
If you screw up your dates tomorrow,
it'll trouble everyone.
All right.
Reine, tomorrow starts at 10, right?
Yeah.
Your first date... is Kotori.
I see, that's why--
Y-You're so wrong!
I just, as the commander...
What are you spaced out for?
Go to bed already!
Return. I have come home now.
Yuzuru!
What was your urgent business?
Trivial. It was nothing too important.
It's time...
Haniel.
First, one person...
Can you actually guess who I am?
Before everyone is gone...
What's the deal, this
early in the morning...?
Shido!
K-Kaguya?
She's gone...
When I woke up, Yuzuru was gone!
How's Kaguya?
Calmer than this morning.
To be safe, I'm having Tohka
and Yoshino stay with her,
so I think she's okay.
Yuzuru was taken to Ratatoskr HQ
for an urgent exam.
Or so we'll say...
Though if Kaguya is Natsumi disguised,
it's a completely pointless lie.
So, Reine?
Who did take Yuzuru?
Was it Natsumi after all?
Yeah, look at this...
This is...
A video from an autonomous camera.
The 12 people Natsumi identified
are being watched around the clock.
This is from midnight last night.
At this point, it looks normal to me.
It's soon.
That's Natsumi's...!
Yuzuru!
As you can see...
Yuzuru was taken by Natsumi's Angel.
It's likely that the real person
Natsumi is impersonating...
...was also erased like so.
Tsk... Natsumi...
Why would you do this?
Finding out her intentions can wait.
We must focus to ensure
there's no more victims.
I believe in Natsumi.
That this is just a game...
Which is why I'm putting an end to this.
Before anyone else disappears...
That's right, Shido.
Let's not spare any effort.
It's about time that we begin our date.
However, in the days that come after...
I'm made to know how powerless I really am.
"Episode Three:
'You're Natsumi'"